SITI RAIHANI AL-ASYURA

HIGH SCHOOL STUDENT

Jakarta, Indonesia | asitiraihani@gmail.com | +6285776443966

SUMMARY

I am a 12th-grade student at SMAN 81 Jakarta, majoring in Engineering, with a strong interest in programming and web development. I have experience working on simple web projects and have been an IT intern at a school student company.

EDUCATION

81 Senior High School

July 2022 - Present

Engineering major

• Relevant to Web Development and Computer Networks.

80 Junior High School

July 2019 - July 2022

- Graduated as one of the finalists in the Indonesian Language Olympiad
- Graduated having served twice in the Student Council (OSIS)

EXPERIENCE

IT Intern, Sievasco Student Company

August 2023 - May 2024

During my internship at Sievasco Student Company, I had the opportunity to enhance my skills in game design and development. I focused on using Unity and Blender to create engaging virtual reality (VR) experiences. My key responsibilities included:

- Assisted in the development of interactive games using Unity and Blender.
- Learned to design and create game prototypes playable in virtual reality (VR).
- Collaborated with team members to refine game mechanics and user experiences.
- Developed skills in 3D modeling and animation for game design projects.

Vice Chairman, School Flag Ceremony Team

August 2023 - August 2024

- · Led and organized flag-raising ceremonies.
- Able to adapt and understand how to behave with the other 58 members
- Ensured all team members were well-prepared and coordinated.
- Collaborated with school officials and other teams to promote discipline and teamwork.
- Developed leadership skills while fostering a sense of responsibility and commitment to school events.

SKILLS

- Basic Programming (Python, HTML, CSS)
- Software Operation (Microsoft Office, Uniti, Blender), Graphic design (Canva and Adobe), Video editing (Capcut, Alight Motion, VN Video Editor, Wondershare Filmora, Blender)
- · Basic Understanding of Computer Networks
- Leadership in Organisasion

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- Languages: English
- Awards/Activities: 3rd Runner-up of LKBB Competition for Jabodetabek
- **Organisation**: *Epic 3.0(2023), Epic 4.0(2024), Pancawarna(2024)*
- Soft Skill: Communication, Teamwork, Leadership, Adaptability, Time management, Public speaking, Emotional intelligence